Prosper Lolo

Freelancer

PROFILE

I am a young man who is motivated to make a success out of himself. I take pride in whatever I engage myself in so that it is done to the best of my abilities. I am task and goal orientated, work well under pressure, and don't mind going the extra mile to achieve the desired results. I would like to gain experience and hopefully become the best at what I do.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Self-Employed

2022

- Develop applications and websites.
- Design websites giving a good user interface and user experience
- Graphic Designer

Developer

Cobweb Developers

2021 - present

- Design, develop and deliver websites and applications to clients according to specifications.
- Managed the database of the company.

Freelancer

Self-Employed

2020 - 2021

• Worked in a team as a frontend developer

SKILLS

Hard Skills

Html/CSS

JavaScript

React

NodeJS

PHP

MySQL

UI/UX Design

Python

Adobe

C++

Soft Skills

Communication skills

Punctuality

Problem-solving

Critical thinking

Teamwork



CONTACTS

Phone: (+27) 659 444 353

Email: loloprosper17@gmail.com

Website: Coming Soon!!

LinkedIn: Prosper Lolo

Address: 76 Albert Street, Marshalltown

Johannesburg, 2111

EDUCATION

2021-Present

BSc in Computer Science and Informatics University of Johannesburg

2014 - 2018

National Senior Certificate

Queens High School

LANGUAGES

English ••••

French •••00

Swahili •••00

References: To be provided if needed